Well, nothing says honesty like taking the fifth,
and Doc, let's try something.
What day of the week is it today?
On the advice of counsel,
I respectfully decline to answer based upon my rights
under the Fifth Amendment to the Constitution.
Oh, color tie you're wearing.
On the advice of counsel,
I respectfully decline to answer based upon my rights
under the Fifth Amendment to the Constitution.
What color is the carpet in front of you?
On the advice of counsel,
I respectfully decline to answer based upon my rights
under the Fifth Amendment to the Constitution.
Let's just get one thing straight.
You don't have any rights under the Fifth Amendment
because you've been pardoned, as you very well know,
as a Supreme Court has been clear for a century and more,
Brown versus Walker, 1896.
When he has been pardoned,
he may not stand upon his privilege.
You know that,
your lawyers sitting behind you
now shifting nervously in their chairs, they know it.
This isn't about the Constitution,
this isn't about the law, this is about contempt.
For this body and contempt for the American people.
But I think I know why you're doing it.
It's because you don't want to answer questions.
It's because you did all kinds of terrible things.
It's because during the pandemic, you got rich, didn't you?
You got rich while people were dying,
hundreds of thousands of Americans over a million
in the end and you were getting rich
and not only were you doing that,
you were using federal employees with taxpayer money
to apply for and solicit cash prizes for you personally,
cash prizes totaling over a million dollars.
You did all of that during the pandemic, didn't you?
That's a question.
On the advice of counsel,
I respectfully decline to answer based upon my rights
under the Fifth Amendment to the Constitution.